All right, now called to order the regularly scheduled meeting of the State's Plan of State Council on Tuesday July 1st.
Number two, public input on scheduled virtual periods.
Number three, claims.
Make motion of route.
Second.
Jones.
Aye.
Barnes.
He's that.
Number four, minutes from the June 11th, 2025 special meeting in June 17th, 25 regularly.
Make motion.
Second.
Jones.
Aye.
Barnes.
Number five, minutes to the moment area, economic development service.
Made outside of organization contract to provide services for fiscal year 2526.
Thank you.
Make motion of route.
Second.
Jones.
Aye.
Barnes.
East.
Aye.
All right.
Number six, memorandum of understanding with auto-economic interest authority for dispatch services.
Ms. Valerie Berger.
Sorry.
This is going to be the same thing on the menu.
With the exception of paragraph three, which gives an additional $40,000 for dispatch rates increase.
No, he's going to say thank you to them, I guess.
Thank you.
Thank you to them.
I'm going to do the opposite.
It's going to help us.
It's another partnership.
You know, we have there that we're.
I personally want to thank the 911 board.
And I absolutely want to thank the dispatchers.
And you.
You guys do an outstanding job.
And if people don't know what you do, they need to go out there and set just for an hour.
And they'll pull their head out and they'll be bald like the chief.
So I'll make a motion to approve.
Aye.
Jones.
Barnes.
Aye.
On seven, contract to go to the county sheriff's department office for dispatch services.
Again, this is the same as last year.
I'm going to give you advice for two dispatchers, which are in the south.
Which you dispatch.
Motion to.
Thank you.
Number eight.
Resolution CC-2025-07.
The CMIA has a mitigation plan.
I've dated 2025-2030.
I'm going to go in.
Good evening.
We have the tentative approval from FEMA.
Based on your resolution tonight.
I will send that to you.
The MIMA Code of Statistics of down there.
It was already been sent to FEMA.
So once I get to send it,
we would get an approval
in our hazard mitigation plan,
which allows us to apply for FEMA grants
and other grants.
We'll be approved for the next five years and two.
And it said,
Is it going to put that into packet?
I'm very interested in it.
The omelet will help you.
Each of them.
Thanks for all the work you did in motion.
I'll set it.
Hi.
Okay, item nine discussion.
The action is 2025-060616.
The pressure of the conservation article won 16-sixton 16-2.
We're building chapter 16 and 164 providing
severability providing conflict provisions.
We're appealing all conflict ordinances
and declaring an emergency regarding rules and regulations
for the operation of parks and recreational facilities of this city.
And this also, I'll take it out along.
Because we have not had ordinances at the park for the last time.
I wish you a lot of item to nine groups.
We're looking for a motion for an emergency action.
Okay.
On a nine.
We're looking for the emergency.
And so, give.
It was just a little bit of background on that, so we all understand what's going on.
Just read your digest.
For whatever reason, the marks audiences are repealed all except for stung ill fish shapes.
Through the bill fishing and the pool.
I assume there was a reason for that, but.
Motion to approve.
It's like a simple farm type.
I'm looking for an emergency motion to approve the ordinance.
I'm going to.
So.
Jones.
Barnes.
I don't call.
I.
Thank you.
Mr.
I'm 11.
You're going to doubt that my own public school superintendent to replace any
Iverson and serve ex officio on the Miami Community Facilities Authority.
Motion to approve.
Okay.
So.
Jones.
Barnes.
I.
All right.
Number 12.
Any other new business, which has a risen since the post office agenda.
13 staff reports.
14 mayor and council committee announcements.
Again, I want to thank the dispatchers for the job they do.
People don't understand.
Being an officer and being out in the field.
I see what's going on.
They set behind the council in a room.
They don't see what's going on.
And if you're involved in a shooting or whatever.
Third.
Probably more scared than what we would be out in the field.
And they do a fantastic job.
They keep it together.
Vows a great supervisor for the for the dispatchers after.
And again, I want to personally thank you guys for the job you do.
I'm going to say something about bless the absence.
Number 15.
Senior managers communication.
I'm just reminded of the.
With the July fireworks event.
I'm going to put around.
I'm going to be hanging out for your.
Do I get to drive the girl car?
Is there going to be a potato?
Yes.
We'll be off the table.
What time.
What time we need to be there?
Six o'clock.
You know, it's not to be a lot of driving off court.
You're so everybody knows.
Wow.
Anything else to add?
All right.
Make a 60 in the German motion.
Second.
Five.
One more.